https://www.abc-knitting-patterns.com/other-privacy-policy.html

Menu
Free Knitting and Crochet Patterns from Elaine Phillips
Privacy Statement for ABC Knitting Patterns
ABC Knitting Patterns has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: ABC Knitting Patterns
Personal Information
This Web site does not generally collect any personal information that can identify you or that can be used to contact you directly. The only exception is our e-mail notification service, which is used to inform subscribers about new additions to the website. This is the only purpose for which we will ever use your e-mail. Your e-mail wll never be disclosed to any third parties.
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org
Download PDF
View Comments
Mailing List
Enter your e-mail to receive new patterns:
Menu
Advanced Search
Home
Newest Patterns
Patterns
Crochet
Accessories
Afghans
Mailing List
Enter your e-mail to receive announcements of new free patterns:
Or follow us using:
Social Media:
Copyright (c) ABC Knitting Patterns. All rights reserved.
The knitting patterns, crochet patterns and other content displayed on this website are the exclusive property of the owner of abc-knitting-patterns.com, and may not be copied, distributed or reproduced without express written permission.
